module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'From what Latin word do we get our word "Trivia"?', 
    a: 'Triumvarate',
    b: 'Tripoli',
    c: 'Trivium',
    d: 'Trivum',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What 3 disciplines made up the Trivium?', 
    a: 'grammar logic rhetoric',
    b: 'geometry astronomy music',
    c: 'science geography P.E.',
    d: 'home-room shop off-periods',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What publication first used the word "trivia" to refer to the game as we know it today?', 
    a: 'The Harvard Review',
    b: 'The New York Times',
    c: 'Columbia Daily Spectator',
    d: 'Yale Daily News',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Ed Goodgold & Dan Carlinsky wrote what popular book about trivia?', 
    a: 'Interesting Tidbits and Facts',
    b: 'Trivia',
    c: 'Random Information',
    d: 'CAT',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'In what year was Trivial Pursuit created?', 
    a: '1950',
    b: '1964',
    c: '1968',
    d: '1979',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'In what country did Trvial Pursuit originate?', 
    a: 'USA',
    b: 'Canada',
    c: 'England',
    d: 'France',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who created Trivial Pursuit?', 
    a: 'Chris Hanson',
    b: 'Chris Hemsworth',
    c: 'Chris Amrstrong',
    d: 'Chris Haney',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What popular trivia related game show was cancelled in 1964?', 
    a: 'Dotto',
    b: 'The $64000 Question',
    c: 'Jeopardy!',
    d: 'Twenty One',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What year was Jeopardy! re-released?', 
    a: '1979',
    b: '1980',
    c: '1984',
    d: '1985',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What does CAT stand for?', 
    a: 'Cats Allowing Telepathy',
    b: 'Carefully Adjancent Things',
    c: 'Carpool Apple Toss',
    d: 'Completely Absurd Trivia',
    answer: 'd'
  },
];